const Chemistry_Question = [
  {
    Question_Text: "The enthalpy of neutralisation of a weak monoprotic acid HA in 1M solution with a strong base is - 55.956 kJ/mole. If the unionized acid requires 1.4 kJ/mole heat for its complete ionization, the dissociation constant of HA is (The heat of neutralisation of strong monobasic acid with a strong mono acidic base is - 57.3 kJ/mole)",
    Options: ["3.2 * 10^(-3)", "1.6 * 10^(-3)", "3.2 * 10^(-4)", "1.6 * 10^(-4)"],
    Answer: 1,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Thermodynamics and Equilibrium"],
    Level: 1,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "1 litre flask contains nitrogen along with a drop of water at 40° C, the total pressure being 760 Torr. If all the contents are transfered to another flask of 0.5L at the same temperature. The pressure of nitrogen setup in the second flask will be (aqueous tension at 40° C = 55 torr)",
    Options: ["1410 torr", "1465 torr", "1520 torr", "1540 torr"],
    Answer: 2,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "States of Matter and Gaseous State"],
    Level: 2,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "The E° is the given diagram is",
    Options: ["0.52", "0.61", "0.74", "0.83"],
    Answer: 3,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Thermochemistry"],
    Level: 4,
    Image: "https://imgur.com/a/BtjWT2e",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "A crystal is made of particles X, Y and Z. X forms FCC packing, Y occupies all octahedral voids of X and Z occupies all tetrahedral voids of X. If all the particles along one body diagonal are removed, then the formula of crystal would be",
    Options: ["XYZ2", "X2YZ2", "X8Y4Z5", "X5Y4Z8"],
    Answer: 0,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Atomic Number"],
    Level: 3,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "1 mole of equimolar mixture of ferric oxalate and ferrous oxalate will require x mole of KMnO in acidic medium for complete oxidation, x is",
    Options: ["0.6 mole", "0.9 mole", "0.3 mole", "1.8 mole"],
    Answer: 2,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Stoichiometry"],
    Level: 4,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "In a reaction aA ---> products, the rate is doubled when the concentration of A is increased 4 times. If 50% of the reaction occurs in 1414 sec, how long would it takes for the completion of 75% reaction starting with same conc of A",
    Options: ["4242 sec", "2825 sec", "2414 sec", "2121 sec"],
    Answer: 0,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "chemical kinetics"],
    Level: 1,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "0.004 M Na2SO4 is iso-osmotic with 0.01 M glucose. Degree of ionization of Na2SO4 is",
    Options: ["25%", "50%", "75%", "85%"],
    Answer: 0,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Stoichiometry"],
    Level: 3,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "A radioactive isotope 'X' with half-life of 6.93 * 10^9 years decay to a stable 'Y'. A sample of rock from the moon was found to contain both elements 'X' and 'Y' in the mole ratio 1 : 7. The age of rock is",
    Options: ["2.072 * 10^10 years", "1.94 * 10^10 years", "1.33 * 10^9 years", "10^10 years"],
    Answer: 3,
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Atomic Structure"],
    Level: 2,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "What is the atomic number of Hydrogen?",
    Options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    Answer: "1",
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Atomic Number"],
    Level: 0,
    Image: "",
  },
  {
    Question_Text: "What will be the order of acidity of the following compounds?",
    Options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    Answer: "1",
    Tags: ["Chemistry", "Organic Chemistry"],
    Level: 1,
    Image: "https://imgur.com/362Q5jg",
  }
];
